<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title>Laser - 标签 - DAY By DAY</title><link>liudongdong1.github.io/tags/laser/</link><description>Laser - 标签 - DAY By DAY</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>zh-CN</language><managingEditor>3463264078@qq.cn (LiuDongdong)</managingEditor><webMaster>3463264078@qq.cn (LiuDongdong)</webMaster><copyright>This work is licensed under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial 4.0 International License.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Tue, 19 Jan 2021 11:19:34 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="liudongdong1.github.io/tags/laser/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>PaperRelative</title><link>liudongdong1.github.io/paperrelative/</link><pubDate>Tue, 19 Jan 2021 11:19:34 +0000</pubDate><author>liudongdong1</author><guid>liudongdong1.github.io/paperrelative/</guid><description><![CDATA[<div class="featured-image">
        <img src="https://gitee.com/github-25970295/blogImage/raw/master/img/20210501111418.png" referrerpolicy="no-referrer">
      </div>Ahsan, H., Prabhu, A., Deeksha, S. D., Domanal, S. G., Ashwin, T. S., &amp; Reddy, G. R. M. (2014, August). Vision based laser controlled keyboard system for the disabled. In Proceedings of the 7th International Symposium on Visual Information Communication and Interaction (pp. 200-203).
Paper: Keyboard Summary design one such unistroke keyboard system with optimized character placement based on frequenctly used digraphs and trigraphs. Module Calibration: purpose: the angle and position of the keyboard can change every time it&rsquo;s set up, so its necessary to know how the exact position and size of the captured keyboard; Methods: Input: a captured frame; set of points representing the corners of the keyboard; convert captured frame to hsv; define the range for blue color detection; get the contours that lie within the range; filter the contours based on area; store the center of each of these contours; calibrate the keyboard angle; Calibrate keyboard angle: input: set of points representing the corners of the keyboard; output: the calibrated keyboard; sort all the points according to x distance; divide sorted points into 3 parts as: left(0-6), mid(7-14), right(15-21) each part: sort based on y distance; sort consecutive pairs of points based x distance; Tracker the laser: using the average of a fixed number of frames to represent the position; CamK: Camera-based Keystroke Detection and Localization for Small Mobile Devices.]]></description></item><item><title>VirtualKeys</title><link>liudongdong1.github.io/virtualkeys/</link><pubDate>Sat, 18 Jan 2020 11:19:34 +0000</pubDate><author>liudongdong1</author><guid>liudongdong1.github.io/virtualkeys/</guid><description>&lt;div class="featured-image">
&lt;img src="https://gitee.com/github-25970295/blogImage/raw/master/img/image-20210119174241375.png" referrerpolicy="no-referrer">
&lt;/div>基于OpenCV，结合图像摄像头、980nm一字红外激光、980nm红外滤光片以及键盘投影激光组成，使用加装了980nm红外滤光片的图像摄像</description></item><item><title>infraredsensor</title><link>liudongdong1.github.io/infraredsensor/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>liudongdong1</author><guid>liudongdong1.github.io/infraredsensor/</guid><description>&lt;div class="featured-image">
&lt;img src="https://gitee.com/github-25970295/blogImage/raw/master/img/20210501111355.png" referrerpolicy="no-referrer">
&lt;/div>红外传感器又叫位移传感器，红外距离传感器一般都在手机听筒的两侧或者是在手机听筒凹槽中，这样便于它的工作。当用户在接听或拨打电话时，将手机靠近</description></item></channel></rss>